Hello guys.  Um, today I will show you
how to pay Sunlife insurance through
GCash.  So it's easy.  Um,
just follow this step by step.  So the
first step is to open your GCash
account.
Just click on your Gcash
account and then after login and
input your pin.
After that, we can log in to
your account.  And then after you have
to click bills.
The others go straight to insurance, but
I want us to go to bills so
we can add them to our
favorites.  That's it.  These are
my favorite billers.  If you notice,
our family has a sunlife policy.  And there's
more.  That's it.  So this is all
you see.  So let's add
one more.  So add biller.  When you click
the add biller,
this is what will appear to you.  So you
have to search Sunlife of Canada
Philippines Ink.  So that's the one with the
Sunlife logo.  Just click on that.  And
then after
here in this portion you have to
input the details.  Your policy number,
um your name if you are the policy
holder and the amount or
our premium.
Um, I'm also inputting here what
the nickname of the account is.  So if
you noticed earlier, the
nicknames on our account were Daddy's
Health Plan, Mommy's Health Plan, that's it.
So in this account we're creating,
we can put it in Mommy's retirement fund
or my retirement fund.  And then
you will also enter when you
want GCash to remind you of the payment,
whether it's every 15th of the month, 30th or any
date.  After you fill out
this portion, you have to click
save.
And after saving,
we will confirm if all
the details we input are correct.  If
our amount, policy number,
policy holder, and email address are correct,
that's where the proof that
you paid will go.  So
he is also important.  So for others, it's
optional, but it's better if
our email is also on a loop,
right?  And then after that, let's confirm
all the details again.
There and then click next.
That's it.
So uh we could proceed paying your
um policy
and then it's done.  It's that
easy.  So thank you for using GCash.
Then your next payment will be in GCash.
No need to input your policy number,
your name and all because it's already in
our favorites.  So just click on
the icon for which account is the
nickname of your policy like the one below
, daddy's health plan,
mommy's health plan.  So
just click on which one.
All your details are there, then
just confirm, confirm, and next, and then it's
done.  So congratulations.  I hope
you learned a lot
from our tutorial on how to use sunl
gcash in sunlife payment.  Thank you.  God
bless.
।